{
    "menonneerajlo2@gmail.com": {
        "chat_1": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "Is the haemoglobin within its reference range?",
                    "response": "Based on the data provided, the result for the haemoglobin (HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)) is 83 g/dL, which falls within the reference range of 120-150 g/dL. Therefore, the haemoglobin is within its reference range."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "is the pcv within its reference range?",
                    "response": "According to the data, the PCV (Packed Cell Volume) result is 26.7, and the reference range is 36.0-46.0. Since the result is outside this range (low), the PCV is not within its reference range."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! How can I help you today? Would you like to know something about the test results or have any specific questions about the data?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"(Photometric Measurement)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Denveu)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"250.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance plus Microscopy)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance)\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_2": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "is the haemoglobin value within its reference range?",
                    "response": "According to the data, the haemoglobin (HB%) value is 83 g/L, and the reference range is 120-150 g/L. Therefore, the haemoglobin value is below the reference range."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "what does mcv mean?",
                    "response": "According to the data provided, MCV stands for Mean Corpuscular Volume. It is a measure of the average size of red blood cells, expressed in liters (L). There is a reference range for MCV, which is typically considered to be 83.0-101.0 L."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "what does mchc mean?",
                    "response": "According to the test results, MCHC stands for Mean Corpuscular Hemoglobin Concentration, which is a measure of the average concentration of hemoglobin within red blood cells. The reference range for MCHC is 31.5-34.5%. \n\nIn simple terms, MCHC measures the amount of hemoglobin in each red blood cell, which is essential for carrying oxygen throughout the body."
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"(Photometric Measurement)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Derived)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"250.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance plus Microscopy)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance)\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_3": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm here to help answer any questions you may have about the provided test results data. What would you like to know?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hello",
                    "response": "Hello! I'm here to help answer any questions you might have based on the test results data. What would you like to know?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "ca-125?",
                    "response": "CA-125: 0.2 U/mL"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "ca 19.9?",
                    "response": "According to the test results, the CA 19.9 level is 2 U/mL.\n\nThe reference range for CA 19.9 is less than 37 U/mL, so this result suggests that the level is within the normal range."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hello! I'm happy to help you with any questions you may have about the test results or any other topics!"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hello! How can I help you today? I'm a helpful assistant, and I have access to a dataset containing various test results. What would you like to know or ask about?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm here to help. If you have any questions about the test results I have, feel free to ask."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm happy to help you with any questions you may have. I sense that you may be interested in getting information about medical test results. The data I have access to contains test results for various biomarkers, along with their corresponding units, reference ranges, and notes. What would you like to know? Are you looking for information about a specific biomarker or test result?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm happy to help you with your questions. From the provided data, I'm assuming you're looking at medical test results. What would you like to know about these test results? Which specific test or marker would you like me to provide information about?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm happy to help you with any questions or concerns you may have. Is there a specific question you'd like to ask about the test results data I have here?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm a helpful assistant here to assist you. What would you like to know or discuss based on the test results provided?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! How can I help you today?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm here to help with any questions you may have. We have a dataset of test results for various bio-markers, such as CA 15-3, CA 19.9, and more. What would you like to know or ask about the results?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_4": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm here to help answer any questions you may have based on the test results data provided. What would you like to know?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! I'm here to help answer any questions you may have. If you're looking for information on a specific bio-marker or test result, I'd be happy to help you with that. Please let me know how I can assist you!"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hello",
                    "response": "Hello! I'm happy to help you with your queries. I've been trained on the provided data about test results, which includes various bio-markers, their results, units, reference ranges, and notes. What would you like to know or ask?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_5": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "what is CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen?",
                    "response": "According to the test results, CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen refers to the bio_marker which has a result of 12.6 U/mL with a reference range of \"Less than 31.3 U/mL\"."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hello",
                    "response": "Hello! How can I assist you today? Would you like to know something about the test results provided? Maybe you'd like to ask a specific question or search for a specific bio_marker's result? Let me know and I'll do my best to help!"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hello! I'm happy to help you with any questions you have. You can ask me about the test results data I have access to, and I'll do my best to provide you with the information you need. What would you like to know?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "what is your name?",
                    "response": "I'm just a helpful assistant, I don't have a personal name. I'm here to assist you with your questions based on the provided data about test results. How can I help you today?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_6": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_7": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_8": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_9": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_10": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_11": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_12": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_13": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_14": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_15": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "is the haemoglobin within its reference range?",
                    "response": "Sorry, there is no haemoglobin mentioned in the provided data. The data only includes information on various biomarkers such as CA 15-3, CA 19.9, and others, but not haemoglobin. Haemoglobin levels are typically tested and reported separately from these other biomarkers."
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 24.5,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_16": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "is the haemoglobin value within its reference range?",
                    "response": "According to the test result, the Haemoglobin (HB%) value is 83 g/L. The reference range for Haemoglobin is 120-150 g/L. Therefore, the value is below the reference range, indicating that it is abnormal."
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "33",
                    "response": "I couldn't find any information that matches the input \"33\". Would you like me to help you with your question related to blood test results?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "00",
                    "response": "I couldn't find any information related to your message \"00\". Can I help you with asking a question or providing information from the test results?\n\nFor example, you could ask me about a specific bio_marker's result or its reference range?"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "44",
                    "response": "I apologize, but there is no information in the provided data that matches the value \"44\". If you're looking for information about a specific bio-marker, you can ask me questions like \"What is the reference range for HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)?\", or \"What is the result for RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH?\". I'll do my best to provide you with the information you're looking for."
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"Derived\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"250.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_17": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hello! How can I assist you? Would you like to ask a specific question or explore the test results data provided? I'm here to help!"
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "shlom",
                    "response": "It seems like you've only typed a name, \"Shlom\". If that's the case, I'm happy to help answer any questions you may have. Could you please clarify what you would like to know regarding the test results provided? Would you like me to help with a specific query or provide information on a particular topic?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"250.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_18": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hello! I'm happy to help you with any questions you may have about the test results provided. Please feel free to ask me anything!"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"Derived\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"150.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_19": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"250.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_20": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"(Photometric Measurement)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Derived)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"150.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance plus Microscopy)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pl\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Electrical Impedance)\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_21": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n\"test_results\": [\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 15-3 Cancer Antigen\",\n    \"result\": 12.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31.3\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA 19.9\",\n    \"result\": 2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 37\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CA-125\",\n    \"result\": 0.2,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 35\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"CARCINO EMBRYONIC ANTIGEN (CEA)\",\n    \"result\": 1.5,\n    \"units\": \"ng/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALPHA FETO PROTEIN (AFP)\",\n    \"result\": 2.54,\n    \"units\": \"U/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.5-5.5\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"P GAMMA GLUTAMYL TRANSFERASE (GGT)\",\n    \"result\": 36.6,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 38\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALKALINE PHOSPHATASE\",\n    \"result\": 120.5,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"45-129\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 0.31,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.3-1.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN - DIRECT\",\n    \"result\": 0.1,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 0.4\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ASPARTATE AMINOTRANSFERASE (SGOT)\",\n    \"result\": 25.4,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 31\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALANINE TRANSAMINASE (SGPT)\",\n    \"result\": 31.9,\n    \"units\": \"U/L\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"Less than 34\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"ALBUMIN - SERUM\",\n    \"result\": 4.27,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"3.2-4.8\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"PROTEIN - TOTAL\",\n    \"result\": 7.66,\n    \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"5.7-8.2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"BILIRUBIN (INDIRECT)\",\n    \"result\": 0.21,\n    \"units\": \"mg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0-0.9\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"SERUM ALB/GLOBULIN RATIO\",\n    \"result\": 1.26,\n    \"units\": \"Ratio\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.9-2\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL IRON BINDING CAPACITY (TIBC)\",\n    \"result\": 362,\n    \"units\": \"μd\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"215-535\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"IRON\",\n    \"result\": 50,\n    \"units\": \"μg/dL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"50-170\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"TRANSFERRIN SATURATION\",\n    \"result\": 6.77,\n    \"units\": \"%\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"13-45\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n    \"bio_marker\": \"THYROID STIMULATING HORMONE (TSH)\",\n    \"result\": 3.14,\n    \"units\": \"μIU/mL\",\n    \"reference_range\": \"0.35-4.94\",\n    \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n]\n}"
        },
        "chat_22": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "66",
                    "response": "That's a specific value.\n\nIn the context of the test results I have, I think you might be referring to the result value for the bio_marker \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\". According to the test results, the result value for MCV is indeed 66.8 units (which are L/L)."
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"Calculated\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"250.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pl\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        }
    },
    "neeraj_menon@thirdray.ai": {
        "chat_0": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! It seems like we just started our conversation. Is there something specific you'd like to talk about or a question you'd like to ask? I'm here to help!"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": {}
        },
        "chat_1": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "9",
                    "response": "It seems like you entered a random number! If you'd like, I can assist you by answering questions related to the provided test results. Which specific aspect of the test results would you like to know more about? Do you have a specific bio-marker in mind, or would you like me to provide an overall summary or help you identify any potential concerns?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/dL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"150.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_2": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "1",
                    "response": "I'm not sure what you are referring to. There is no data provided. Can you please provide some data or ask a question, and I'll do my best to help?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": {}
        },
        "chat_3": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "1",
                    "response": "You're asking about the first test result, which is HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%).\n\nAccording to the data, the result is 83 g/L, and the normal reference range is 120-150 g/L."
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Derived)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"250.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        },
        "chat_4": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "4",
                    "response": "It seems like you've provided some numbers! However, without any specific context or input, I'm not sure what you would like me to assist you with. Could you please provide some more information or clarify your question?"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": {}
        },
        "chat_5": {
            "prompts": [
                {
                    "prompt": "",
                    "response": ""
                },
                {
                    "prompt": "hi",
                    "response": "Hi! How can I help you today? Would you like me to assist you in answering a question or provide information about test results? Just let me know!"
                }
            ],
            "extracted_data": "{\n  \"test_results\": [\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HAEMOGLOBIN (HB%)\",\n      \"result\": 83,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"120-150\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED BLOOD CELL COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 3.99,\n      \"units\": \"million/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"3.84-8\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PCV (PACKED CELL VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 26.7,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"36.0-46.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"HEMATOCRIT\",\n      \"result\": null,\n      \"units\": \"\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"\",\n      \"note\": \"(Calculated)\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCV (MEAN CORPUSCULAR VOLUME)\",\n      \"result\": 66.8,\n      \"units\": \"L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"83.0-101.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCH (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN)\",\n      \"result\": 20.8,\n      \"units\": \"pg\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"27.0-32.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"MCHC (MEAN CORPUSCULAR HAEMOGLOBIN CONCENTRATION)\",\n      \"result\": 31.5,\n      \"units\": \"g/L\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"31.5-34.5\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"RED CELL DISTRIBUTION WIDTH\",\n      \"result\": 18.7,\n      \"units\": \"%\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"11.6-14.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"PLATELET COUNT\",\n      \"result\": 284,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/uL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"150.0-450.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    },\n    {\n      \"bio_marker\": \"TOTAL LEUKOCYTE COUNT (TLC)\",\n      \"result\": 5.7,\n      \"units\": \"Thous/pL\",\n      \"reference_range\": \"4.0-10.0\",\n      \"note\": \"\"\n    }\n  ]\n}"
        }
    }
}